import { quizQuestions } from '../types/quiz'
export const marvelquestionlist: quizQuestions[] = [
    {
        question: 'Which MCU movie featured Spider-Man’s first appearance?',
        options: ['Spider-Man: Homecoming', 'Captain America: Civil War','Iron Man 3', 'Avengers: Age of Ultron'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these characters did NOT appear in Phase One? ',
        options: ['Thor', 'Black Widow', 'Captain America','Black Panther'],
        answer: 4
    },
    {
        question: 'Which war did Captain America fight in? ',
        options: ['World War I', 'World War II', 'Iraq War','Vietnam War'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'What legislation requires superhumans to be governed by law? ',
        options: ['Paris accord', 'Latveria accord', 'Sokovia accord','Crimea accord'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Where did Scott Lang work before becoming Ant-Man?',
        options: ['Baskin Robbins','Jamba Juice', 'Chipotle','McDonald’s'],
        answer: 1
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these characters is NOT in Doctor Strange? ',
        options: ['Kaecilius', 'Wong', 'Thanos','Lucian'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Who is the main villain in Spider-Man: Homecoming? ',
        options: ['Mysterio', 'Vulture', 'Kraven','Venom'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which movie was the Falcon’s first appearance? ',
        options: ['Iron Man 2', 'Avengers: Age of Ultron', 'Captain America: The Winter Soldier','The Avengers'],
        answer: 3
    },
    {
        question: 'Which planet are Thor and the Hulk on in Thor: Ragnarok? ',
        options: ['Knowhere', 'Sakaar', 'Asgard','Xandar'],
        answer: 2
    },
    {
        question: 'Which of these movies came first? ',
        options: ['Ant-Man', 'Captain America: Civil War', 'Doctor Strange','Guardians of the Galaxy Vol. 2'],
        answer: 1
    }
];